Everyone told me to calm down.
I came in a hurry and they told me to calm down and that everything would be okay.
It was a patrol.
A little bit.
So...
Well...
The live feed...
For the past two weeks?
Yes, sir.
I'm sure they're waiting for you.
Shall we go?
Live?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Hey.
Today, I have to say something.
I'm your teacher today, too.
I'm your master again today. - Pleased to meet you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's been a while since you did a live broadcast?
It's been two weeks.
Live is the best, isn't it? Live is the only way to do it.
Live is the only way to do it. Live is the only way to do it.
And so, as usual, we'd like to get on with the show.
Today is November 22nd.
Tomorrow is a national holiday.
That's right!
You know what day it is, don't you?
There it is!
Another shame.
Yes, it is.
HAJI.
No, well, you don't know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just don't live by dates.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't live by date. I don't live by date.
That's cool. It's like you live by yourself.
It's good when you're like that.
When the sun comes up, you're like, "Okay.
When the sun goes down, you go to bed. That kind of thing.
Tomorrow is Labor Thanksgiving Day.
November.
November 23rd. So that means...
Thanksgiving Day is the 23rd and the 24th are Sundays.
I wonder if there's any change of plans... because it's a Saturday.
No Saturday?
Because it's not a holiday.
Saturday is only Sunday?
That's right. That's right.
In this day and age.
And of course, it's November 23rd, Labor Thanksgiving Day.
But it's also...
It's also Good Samaritan's Day.
Good brother?
Tomorrow... You have a brother.
Is your brother a good brother?
He's a good brother.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you for treating me to yakiniku.
Nice. Fun.
I'd like to meet him once. Any chance you'll let me.
I'd love to. I'd love to.
But maybe... you know...
There's a chance you and I might get into a fight.
Why?
You're the master, aren't you?
Yes, but he might be a belligerent guy.
That's not true.
He wanted to meet you, too.
He wanted to see you.
I'm just saying, Mom, Dad, you're like me...
We all met.
Come on, Master.
Can I call my dad?
This is really happening!
Where the hell are you! It's like a big fight.
It's chaos.
Yeah, it is, but, hey, good brother.
I have a good brother.
Is your brother a good brother?
He's a good brother!
Thank you for always sending me sweets!
He sends you candy? He's a good brother for sure.
How old is your CCO brother? Four years!
He's older? Four years older!
So, of course, you work and everything? He works, he works hard, he works.
What's your type of person? Uh, in terms of type...
Or? I love trains. I'm a train geek.
And maybe he looks like a train geek in that drama "Train Man"?
Densha Otoko? Is that right?
I'd be in trouble if I went to Yasumoto's house...
My brother and I love each other.
A little more...
I'll do N-gauge with my brother... and my dad.
N-gauge!
No, no, no. With my brother again.
We're very busy.
And my brother likes Enka.
Opera? He also likes Enka and orchestras.
He likes music, too. Maybe we'll talk.
But if my brother, father and I have something to talk about...
It'd be chaos. We'd never run out of things to talk about.
We'd talk like that all the time.
If I said I liked the Warring States period, I'd last a week.
If I say I like the Warring States period, we'll have enough to last a week.
I can't imagine him as that type of guy.
I think he's more like the leader of a tribe or something.
No way! Peaceful brother is peaceful brother!
He's the best brother.
By the way, we were just talking about family, but November 23rd is also Dine Out Day, which is for moms who are always busy with chores and dads who are always doing housework.
I know there are mothers who are always busy with housework and fathers who are always doing housework, but I wanted to relieve them of their work and let them know how much fun it is to eat out with their family once in a while.
Housework.
Let's go out to eat together today.
You're going out to eat with your brothers?
When that happens, what do you talk about with your family?
What? What kind of talk? About what?
We talk about work.
How about you, Master? What do you want to talk about?
Does he have problems? He listens to me a lot.
This is what's bothering him right now. What do you think, Wai-chan? Like that.
He'll ask me what I think.
You're really a soft person, aren't you?
We happened to have a fight on Tanabata Day.
Mom and dad?
And my brother invited me to write my wish on a strip of paper.
I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it...
So, Yaroro-kun...
I'm definitely going to go along for the ride.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have a brother... but I don't know how I feel about that...
I'm the eldest son, so I don't have a book at all, so it's always me, me, me...
I'm the eldest son, so I'm always the one to do the kissing.
If I had an older sister or an older brother, it might have been a little different, or the same, or nothing at all.
It might be the same, or it might not be the same at all.
Well, well, well... if that's the case... it's a good brother's day, so...
If you have an older brother... maybe this is a good opportunity to ask him if he's a good brother...
I'm sure you've had an epiphany... about whether I'm a good brother... or not.
It's a warm day... we can have a dinner out with the family... that's nice...
I'm sure you'll be very happy to hear from us.
Let's go to this corner, shall we?
Yes, that's right.
So, here we go.
Here we have another one for you today, the living creature creation!
Dancing Nippori Ebi-buddy, Arakawa-kun, Tokyo
Thank you very much.
This is the name of the creature I'm about to introduce to you.
This is a very long name!
It's a very long name!
I can't remember it.
"Ryuguu no Otohime no Motome no Genkai no Sanshin" (Cut off the original knot of Ryuguu)
Last time, you saw how the Ryugyu came to be.
The removal of the original knot of Princess Longinus Otokohime.
It's a living thing, isn't it?
Cut it out.
Ex-wife?
She's not my ex-wife, Master.
Divorced? They're divorced.
Ex-Yui's.
What do you mean by ex-wife?
What does it mean?
Ex-Yui, cut off Princess Otohime.
Oh, that's difficult...!
Ryugu no Otohime no Motoyui no Mikkiri.
What are you saying?
What do you mean?
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ryugu no otohime no moto no yukata no kirisotsu no kirisotsu no kirisotsu no kirisotsu.
Well, well, well... it's kind of Ryugu-ish, isn't it?
It's like Ryugu.
Oh man, I'm making a mistake... what am I writing?
Wait a minute.
Ryugu no Otohime!
I really don't like it if it's my ex-wife's.
I really don't like it if it's my ex-wife's...
Isn't that scary?
Scary, scary.
Ex-wife must have left something behind.
Cut it off.
Scary.
Hair or something.
Scary, scary, scary.
Ryu's.
Oh, my God.
Otohime's.
Good night.
Moto yui no kirishimasai... I wonder if there are kanji for this... but I really can't imagine it written in katakana.
I can't believe it's written in katakana.
I'm not sure if it's that easy to understand....
I can cut off the lizard's and fan's tails like this, can't I?
I see... so you're saying she's a lizard... and this is your ex-wife?
I see... that part... it's perfectly fine if the lizard-like thing is cut off.
Yes, that's right... it can live.
So please take care of it.
What's this?
A toilet seat?
Yes...
Is that so?
It's called "Okohime".
There's an Okohime on the toilet.
The one that flushes.
So it's a snail shaped like a toilet.
I see what you mean.
It looks like both a toilet and a snail.
That's right.
I see.
This is a toilet seat.
Yes, it is.
This looks like a tank.
It's a Ryugu, so it's a little bit...
It looks like a rock?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
By the way...
The original knot of "Otohime of Ryugu" is cut out of seaweed.
Seaweed.
Can it be seaweed?
That's for sure, isn't it?
Indeed.
It's alive.
There were some flowers... a little... a little bit... but they were all placed together.
The original of Otohime of Ryugu no Okuhime... the hair... that was cut off... was washed up on the beach like this.
It's thin like a hair, so I cut it off.
So, the original hair of Otohime of Ryugu was cut off.
I can see it all the time, and it's a good thing we can see it all over the Sea of Japan.
I don't know if you're in Yokohama or something, but I heard that there are a lot of cuttings of Ryugu no Otohime no yuan on the coasts of the Honshu area.
Princess Boo-Boo is more of a warlord than a princess.
Boo-Boo...
It just so happens that this week, today too, there is a tree called "Ryugu no Otohime no moto" (Princess Otohime of the Dragon Palace). This is actually the longest name for this plant in Japan.
Wow a. Ryugu no Otohime no Moto.
I've been researching it for a while now, and it's alive and kicking.
I looked it up... the longest name of any living creature...
a. The slender body of a fish called "Okinawa-ki" in Nagano Prefecture.
There's a fish called "a" which has a slender mouth...
The slender part of the mouth is the long, big hagi.
It's like reading haiku or tanka.
It was a question at the end.
Like a hagi with a ukeguchi.
A hundred poems.
A big, long, slender hagi.
By the way, some insects are longer than that.
A long one.
Ryukyu 13-star little big mushroom insect
I wonder if it's tiny.
May I ask you to read a little bit?
Ryukyu 13 star small
Hoshibi
n? star
Hoshi?
Hoshi-chibi big mushroom bug
I couldn't find a picture of it.
I'm pretty sure there is a mushroom beetle that eats mushrooms.
I don't know what it is... but it looks like a gold beetle...
Ryukyu 13-star little big mushroom beetle.
I think it's something like that.
It's Ryukyu, so it's probably from the Southwest Koto line over there.
Okinawa or Tenmoku Oshima...
Maybe he's from there.
They're called 13 stars, so...
So there are 13 stars, or dots.
I'm not sure about the "little" after that.
I guess it means tiny.
Is that what you mean when you say "natural"?
It's a little guy, but then it's a big little bugger.
Either it's little or it's big.
Definitely.
You don't need one or the other, do you?
I don't know what it is.
I don't know. I mean, we could just go with the little guy, right?
Or just a big little bug.
I'm really curious to see what it looks like.
I can't find a picture of it.
Just search for it.
I wonder if anyone knows what it is.
It's the insect with the longest name in Japan.
Of course, people who know about insects know about it, and I'm sure there are pictures.
But this is a mystery... maybe it's hiding something dangerous... like a secret of the country...
Yes, yes, yes, it's like it's holding military secrets.
Chibi-oh something.
Chibi-oh mushrooms?
Chibi-oh Mushroom Worm
No way.
Wow.
I want to find one.
I don't think it's that rare.
Names like that usually have a historical background.
That's right.
The guy who first named it Chibi...
He said, "No, it's not short.
So they named it "Oh.
That kind of thing.
It's like, "Why don't you just call him either one?
It's a big little baby bug.
Well, well, well, well.
Thank you again for all your wonderful work.
Thank you very much!
You're amazing, aren't you?
What's this? It's like an octopus!
No way! What kind of lizard is this?
I've never seen a lizard under the ground before... but it's hard to imagine...
I've seen lizards before... but I've never seen them in action... like this...
But aren't lizards so beautiful?
They're rainbow-colored... rainbow-colored, blue and gold... they're kind of amazing, but they're so beautiful...
They're shining in Japan, so they're probably...
You're moving so fast, you don't think you've been attacked by the enemy, right?
I want to know how lizards feel...
I'd like to know how lizards feel... but why do they stand out?
I don't know, maybe there's one... maybe one.
I'm looking for someone who can talk to lizards. I wonder if there are any lizards.
It's a mystery, isn't it?
Oh, but I'm so glad you're here, thank you very much.
I'm sure some of you came to the Sakami Harafest the other day.
Oh, you're getting good at it. You're getting good at it. Did you learn how to do this little "squeeze"?
I learned it from Hanamichi. The teacher told me not to show my face.
He told me not to show my face. Like that.
I see. Excellent angle.
Well, well, well...
Well, Master, since you're here, if there's anything I can do for those watching the live broadcast...
Yes, please look forward to the next one.
A little fresh.
You're going to do a new kind of gal-pee.
I did.
The angle is really gyaru!
That's what I'm talking about.
You can live in the modern age.
I live in the modern age, too.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'll see you next week.
See you at 8:00 p.m.?
Yes, that's right.
So I'm getting a devil's charge.
Congratulations on your TVK drama, Master & Mr. Balikata!
Thank you very much.
From Mr. Eph of Zadara.
And now...
Of course.
Yes, Balikata.
I'm appearing in a musical the drama "Love Live Scribe" together with Mr. Why Why Why Why Why Why Why Why Why
I'm appearing in the musical the drama, and tvk is going to be broadcasting it.
I hope you are looking forward to it!
I hope you are looking forward to it.
I got to see a little bit of it when he was stabbed in the side.
What's this?
What the hell!
It's a sparkling drama.
There probably won't be any scenes.
Not at all.
The acting is so intense.
That's right.
Yui says you're cute today.
Master, you're so popular these days.
I'm irresistible!
I've been very popular lately.
I've been told I'm cute so that I can deliver the message.
Master, you're in the dating phase.
I'm going through a "gal phase" and I'm going through a "gal phase".
I'm in my gal phase.
Sagami Halloween festival was a lot of fun! festival was a lot of fun!
Thank you so much!
I'm sure you guys will be putting out a lot of towels and stuff.
I'm sure you guys will be putting out towels and stuff like that.
That's nice.
It's great!
I think it's even better than you think, but it makes me too happy.
If there's another chance, I'd love to see you again.
I'd like to see Ebitu-san on stage next time too.
Thank you very much!
Well then, I'll see you next week for the live broadcast. Thank you very much again for this week.
Thank you very much.
Seino
Pishoo!
I don't know what's going on.
I'm sorry, there was a little bit of crap like this.
It's new.
We're the first to bring you...